Tippi gotta. Have.
The end.
Game in.
The US.
Do.
I should have known he was going to dead
when they wheeled him him. With everything
cleaned. Everything. Everything
except save my patient.
Everything in the books.
That I have permission to take over and
try things my way. Embracing room is no
place to experiment is dead I
can't do any harm. And well.
Glosses euros. Do what you want to do
all right. Make an opening into the
chest cavity. By one hundred millions of
current directly the heart then massage my
hand
a little the brain area
by yourself by myself. To
work fast. Too late. Talking will
be still alive. I just pick
up and think how speak
it was often hard. It's electric shock
should stimulate the motor area enough to
elevate the heart again and he will need
any external stimuli keep away from the
motor area paralyze him for good which would
you rather be paralyzed or dead people
starting the heart you've already lost
your patient Dr I'm going to save mine.
Coming back stronger than ever. Thanks
unbelievable to get the nerve to experiment
. I've been working on something like
this for weeks. In the laboratory.
I knew this would work them when I had the
opportunity don't conduct experiments on
people you should be sure
of the results. I have now.
Stop researching heart and see
if I can take over by itself.
Close up the chest. And I finish
with the cerebral area. I'll just
pass down instantly.
And you did perform miracles. I may
not approve of your method but. I am
proud of the result.
It was an amazing. Even an extraordinary
operation son. Still is too risky
to uncontrolled. Saved
his life. After Effects
What about them. If you've lost their
edge to experiment to explore.
Don't explore people before you put
a scalpel to one an operation like this
needs testing under every condition already
over again that it's my monkeys
not people that matter should be
dead now or think so. There's
more to surgery than just being
a carpenter to patch up walls or
a plumbing to drain pipes. Our bodies are
capable of adjusting in ways we widely
dreamt of if we can only find the
key I'm so close now so very
close the key to one
complete transplant patients
to be able to transplant limbs in August
to be able to replace disease and damage
parts of the body as easily as we replace
I colonias now so that the new parts will
join together as though they were
born there. Can Be Done it can
be done. With my new special compound
I created I'll do it I know I can do it
sure sure that's what you say that's what I
know I know I'm close. To
that and so proud of you I could kiss you
promises always promise that I care for
your father's libel to report it. And stop
the flow shown when you do America will
be fun to watch anymore and I can promise
you one thing you know the grandchildren
will be tends to be able. To you
better hurry if you want to catch
a plane to Denver that you know that medical
convention can start without you. Jan
you'd better check about my reservations
Oh yes I'll call the airport I'll be right
there. Below. The line between
scientific genius and obsessive fanaticism.
I want you on the right side if I don't
experiment how can I help
a form operations like the one you almost
messed up but I can't cover up for you
anymore the superintendent had it out
with me he thinks that you always been
stealing those limbs from the amputee
operation so what if it is I've got to have
limbs for my transplant experiments where
you said test an experiment test an
experiment but the all been taken from
people I've got to have them to work with
sure I've made
a few mistakes but I've learned
from them I've learned. Your
reservations are all set to thirty take
a. Pill what have you to plan
for the weekend or nothing much
the quiet weekend you're sure you're not
going out of the country house you're
always sneaking off up that place gives me
the creeps I should have sold when your
mother died you can't sell that place but
I mean it's nice to get away from the
city I can work without anyone stopping
around you spend too much time out there
all right I'll see you both in
a few days at the clean up and get
out of here final Gratian not
them walking on thin ice don't go too far.
Every time you touch me I got my mind
on the key issue you know I want to
get married I can't stand having
you been wonderful I'd rather be
a bride in
a few more weeks nothing will
keep us apart we'll be together.
That's according to. I'm so
glad you're here I was afraid
you'd gotten away there was
a very important the message it came to
you it sounded Kreider just had been
looking everywhere it was from
a man called Kurt he called from the country
today and he said something terrible
it happened he wanted you to
come right out. Thank you.
You've always wanted to know it's kept me
away from you so many weekends that you
got the keys to your car.
I'm
buying
a ticket to take me at the abyss. Because
the things I'm working on don't need an
audience they can come to him or
write or I hold of the questions
for the ministry team I'm will
be there soon enough you'll see
him I've got to hurry.
Era.
The the.
Air.
The There are
a. This
is new. News to lose
them new each.
New new. New New New
New New live in the in.
New
new.
Moon.
You need.
Right all right for God with
all the love I'm coming.
Next. What have you sort of
a life. Saver to savor what is it do you
talk to her please sterilize the tubes in
it she was quickly only going
to do I'm going to have
a look in the closet first so I can know
this is more important but you don't know
there's got to be
a purpose is urgent there was I tell you
before it's too late I can't one first
time arguing with you.
With pain day.
To NEW DAY. Dawning. The.
Man. In
a. Limited
.
Role.
I guess. To the move. East
for. My eyes are deceiving
me what you see is
real What's done is done and what I've
done is right it's the work of some it's.
Members.
Earn it.
I've had success with transplants
now I can do it for her.
As planned at what brought her back
to live and I've got another body
I can make a complete again. Be
a madman and believe that she could ever
be like or don't argue with me I love her
too much come out of state like this
I'll restore us before you'll see.
You realize Can't you see there's
a pattern to all that lives an order
an arrangement she has a heart and
a brain and her spirit was involved
not in one or the other No you are
a brain in
a hundred percent Wackenhut.
State of things you
can remember her love for you. Then how
can you make of her an experimental part.
Of the skill and science I possess
was meant for this life as
a pattern or pattern of my life to shaping
itself to say for now that you intend to
go through with it yes. Sleep don't
rest and grow strong.
How long do you think we can keep her
alive under these conditions forty eight
fifty hours looks to us. And you really
believe you can work and transplant.
Successfully it's. Like my own.
Within the farm. It was an early
experiment that failed with her I'm
using my new adrenal serum must work. I.
Got to go down. If the
police or anyone called.
Sell them you don't know anything about
it. I don't think anyone will trace this
here because your body was burned in the
wreckage. Of course of course Bill before
you got. To have
a look at that cost is the reason
why I called you up you. Keep
it locked. I got so mild and almost
broke out. Through time to keep it
closed.
I think about her now. That the
find her about it oh you're
going to go back anyone.
How you doing. They're always.
There always.
Aid
a way. To
.
Get the.
Whole world all the new
Olu to face.
Do you do.
A Google. Search.
If you. Did it.
In effect.
The you. You.
First.
You know what it's like
being like this. You know
what it's like.
Go there we could have
preferred. What president.
Still untouched. Is keeping
me alive it's given me
a power you can count to have.
A way that you can feel.
Christ the supreme and.
The man.
Than. Together will think.
It is this Are the form of
these. Other will regard.
Create a whole arc and you will have
a forensic. Opinion. I
think.
Rumor.
A little.
A lot.
Of IF IF IF IF IF IF.
If if if if. It's just.
This if it's. Just it's just.
A class paradise still. Or
a. New Normal mind can imagine something
even more terrible than your.
Effort had. I call. Ha'aretz out on that
and backpack. It was
a horrible beyond yours and it's
in there locked behind that door.
The path of experimentation twist and turn
through mountains all miscalculation and
often lose themselves in ever
darkness. Behind that door is the
sum total of Dr Cotton as mistakes.
Happen right bring me
back to that. Perhaps not
who knows. But you know.
Before he injected the serum
into that it was but
a massive gratitude shoes cyclists.
Just lay there weighted down with its
transplants of broken limbs and
amputated arms. With this serum. Began
to breathe
a bath. Would you have thought
possible what he's already done.
Take yourself. He brought
you back you live.
On to
a few years ago. Transplants were
impossible. Actually he's been
doing up here when no one could see his
work yes. There are many with transplants
on death. And on me. But
it can tear away my
flesh time after time test after
test. My hopes shattering with each
grafted on he fasten to me what
you get with the room warp.
Instead of strengthening. You see.
He's learned from his mistakes.
And you stayed with him.
Helping him in his passport that he
claimed I thought that. Was there
a place for me on the outside of this.
World where eyes would look upon me with
pity and people would turn away
from me in disgust. You know.
The alcoholic as is but.
The dope addict is needle.
I had my research. Used to be
a surgeon because my life. And one
night in the laboratory that.
I was an accident. They
had to amputate my arm.
Here is due to. Choice He was my only hope
so you need both his arms not just
one. You see my. Transplanted
grotesqueness stayed so did I. I
think only for the day he can work
a successful transplant to my body
that is why I stay the transplant.
And I head on to another body. And he
said Same with the belief he can do it.
He would put the pictures
of another. Check that is
a foreign substance that
is. Transplant would have
a take it would devastate in place.
And the bodies would get a say
a pack any invading matter. But his
you discovery this you serum change
your. Serum injected into the bloodstream
fix the limb for you to choose.
In the next lymphoid step provide the
antibodies with the blood that detect foreign
transplant to matter. Was tested
on tried to we used it on.
The quote in but being
left of me. Makes me
feel for. You
may produce results it didn't
ask for such as. You mean.
I guess. That's what terrible
then you relative beauty.
Helps our American.
To see that you're at the mercy of every
element of the universe how can you speak
of our. Hair. That's my
question he's got into me.
My brain burned at. Being
inside an iron carriage. I
mean to prove it. Proves
nothing. Powerless
so. I am you.
Are left are.
You know if you hear me. Laugh or.
Whatever you lack. I meant. You
know I. Am only head and you are
whatever you are. Get with trying.
When you're running from what's wrong
with you. It's you. Something wrong
something beyond control in that room
nothing beyond my control she's alive and
I'll keep her alive until I find her
a body. I'm tired I've got
to go to sleep and you.
Didn't find her body well I've got to be
careful I can't afford to be identified as
the last person with
a girl before she disappears do
you think you'll get one. Many
things left for tomorrow.
A whirl. And
for.
You. Who has.
Told. You.
Do who blew.
A hole. A good.
High I was about to call
a cab the way you were looking me over
have you been there oh just find I haven't
seen you for about
a world too long I'm still waiting for
that call you want from me you know how it
is with interns Oh work work and no play
even makes a don't doctors is it a lose
a dead sideman of you want to. Say how
that little side question anatomy or
anything that I'm
a body beautiful content you know they
think model plenty of females on the Iran
who have
a field day which is why not. You're just
what the doctor ordered one jumping.
On second thought I just remembered
I've got to stop by my place and gave
a few things only take
a minute you know Mind you I always
follow the doctor's orders anything you
prescribe I'll take as I like about
you Diana always so obliging.
Here now you going with the very high Gini
we're going to look for somebody. Got
any room for me oh sure plenty builders and
Genie Reynolds genie This is after all
caught up in the press.
As
a matter of fact I can wait. Now the story
you have to wait to see think this safety
in numbers this time the rule. Not to
hurt and I promise not to hurt you.
You know that part of.
Moore Well it looks like we're about ready
to go backstage all five of the girls who
have reached the contest by all and we
are here to choose Miss body beautiful
Now we were limited everyone except the
Bible finalist and they will be judged
solely by your applause so let's bring them
on Bert. Hello to our.
Thank you for.
That bravo to. You
from rags.
Carrying the love.
You so.
Many hours to.
You soon it is the second night of
my idea of the season expecting me you
know another Go figure model remember that
one in school years ago when I had the
accident oh yeah you know Doris. Doris
sure I'll hear people say you know she
just stays in or stew. Posing for our
precious camera. To look.
For others. To mess with bodies or.
Maybe there's a risk on
the. Interior I believe for
a few more hours. To
kill some. More of them of their body.
You hear me.
Hear me. You know how it
goes because I'm trying to.
Infamy upon infamy. Could ever be part of.
Any claims his work especially. Managing.
Trying to push back your own.
Oh you must exist look behind that.
Old.
If you do.
You. Think.
To boost you.
OK boys I've had it for to my Baby One More
Year One more pleased so far this time
just about any.
So Doris would you like to have
a drink with me just you and me away from
everybody some place where nobody nobody
I'm with you and I can really be alone no
thank you all by posting for me private
like
a pay your real money real good money kind
of money they don't throw at you every
day and for doing hardly nothing at all I
do my posing for classes only Wednesdays
and Saturdays eight to
ten but we could night.
See it all Mr The show's over
next time bring a camera and buy
a ticket I'm not running
a charity you know remember me do you
Doris every guy on the NE gives me
that same tired line I'm Bill Carter
Yeah well. Long time ago that
right. Here on with two of
that wise guy approximating fun
of me after my accident is
can we go somewhere and talk no I don't
date men because I pose like I do your mind
works overtime you get ideas
you know are all alike.
No not all of us I'm not on the
make for you OK so maybe you
a better than most maybe
not I still hate all men.
To me but what one did to me once
have you forgotten. Where as you.
Know I haven't forgotten. Neither
have I I carry the memory of
this. But you can't hide yourself away
or forever posing there in front of
a bunch of neurotics Galahad I trusted
a man once Oh the way I wanted to get me
he got his head full of jealous lies and I
got to forget how can I forget I
carry the memory around with me.
I might still appealing
to you now. Still so just
to make you think. You don't
even turn away from the like
everyone else. To me you're
not ugly I see only beauty in you you have
a lovely body and it's basic can
be made beautiful again also. I've
heard that song before I'm
a doctor I know my father is one of the
leading plastic surgeons anyone can help
you we can I know I can I've been to
doctors it's no use the scar tissue is too
deep no one can help me I was
a few years ago today nothing's hopeless
we can grab scar and skin tissue that
we can even freeze areas of the
skin sand away damage skin tissues
when you see that that's look in
your eyes i almost one of these I'm
almost one of these you. Start believing.
I can. Ever go.
Back to see you I have a S.S.
. And the more
awful. Thing you can be is
what terrible than what
I am. I had without
a body. Had to chip in its grave.
I hate him for what he's
done to me. Or match mine.
I have come to be your friend. What
you feed yourself with he prefers.
Less clear link because you're more.
Likely to think I'm afraid of what's in
there. Or a mule. A meat head in search of
a body. People fear with they
don't understand and what they
can't see. What you're
talking about. Nothing but
a couple life. And a freak I'm dead. Why
should I be afraid of a few knocks on
a door. Thank you Ron. You Afraid
of what you imagine lay behind that
door I. Imagine.
It was
a child of crap together the bits and
pieces that were stolen from the hospital.
Potato Dhamma leg a toss So what
are you hoping them together like
a mattress jigsaw puzzle. And
medicine. He said to me that if I buy
a point to shoot. At that no. One that he
was an earlier formula was my successful
as the series using on you but it was
enough to allow the transplants to
take. Your experiment to successful.
It would be my turn and what
else has happened to I'd.
Mean what else. Well it's. Mutated
some of course. It's changed considerably.
Why don't you open the door. See how it's
changed with and you will I warn you
you're going to stop pestering me do you
hear I'm getting fed up with you and your
insidious talk he should have cut
out your time while he was at it.
Radio. No not anymore I
had. No more of it.
Keeps of locked in there so that
it will be safe that's all.
For me.
Beast. People on your existence
it was my time of agony
and with you laughing at.
Your own miserable. And.
Mind.
Even if your father could help me I
couldn't pay him the kind of money it would
take him to talk about money does
a lot of work without any charge
why should you want to do
this when the what's in it for
you. I'm going to make your face
beautiful again cut it off
and give your body away.
I'm sorry Bill. I have been knocked around
so many times I've lost count.
It's tough living with this.
I don't mean to sound grateful because
you've been batted around don't go sour you
should lose your trust in people not
all of us. I believe you I want.
To really think something can be done
only my father knows that we have
a country place just out of town is visiting
for the weekend I could take you there
now for
a consultation you made tonight well if
you'd rather wait till he comes back if you
know no I mean he wouldn't be annoyed being
bothered with me so late at night when
you let me do the worrying I do anything
that'll help me get rid of this face
so that's where I commit. Remember
the last time I helped you.
We're going. To be calling my girlfriend
I want to tell her the news for you know
the verdict is going to bring. You
all right I shouldn't talk until
I know what's going to happen my girlfriend
she supposed to drop him later I'll
have to leave a note or
something or just tell your see
a later Otherwise the last lot of nosy
questions we want to be sure first struck
something on with you and.
Just so you'll keep in touch. Leave
it on the table she'll say you.
Had to go out with all those friends
Bill Clinton. Calling you tomorrow.
I'll leave it on the
last. Day I want to do
that with My Space no luck
probably the lifetime.
I have. So.
You and your father live here only on
weekends and we want to get away from the
city. Place certainly is. Rather
further from prying eyes the better
I mean it's actually quiet here we go
away from the noise and telephones how I
guess it is was about sound off
accidentally. My father should be back so.
You mean he's not here now. Come
on now Doris Do I look like
a maniac goes around killing
a girl I've got to learn to trust people
people like me really I'm sorry I trust
you I trust you with my life.
Like an ass when he was in that.
The right back.
That. Would begin Did they get forgotten
about forgotten you Doris you become very
important to me very important I put
a little water and it would be too
strong for you. I'm not a very have
a drink or my. History or
future whatever it may be
I'll drink to that.
Getting off the learning.
Thing in life.
To bring you
a body. A beautiful one. So.
You can't so I can. Let you as
a complete woman not part of one. This is
a crime to want to keep you alive. It's
a crime for science to jump ahead by
years. This kind of thing must be done.
When it's over you'll see. About the
story no drug aware also should be
awake. When she does come to. Be your
head consciously awakening for her.
Who's going to do it. It's
got to be Goliath here.
Very well.
The of.
The
of the of.
Late.